[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 32, "question": "But to be serious, and I hope the answer is yes because it gives me some succor in this relationship we now have, is being so cool itself a terrible burden?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "TO", "VB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 33, "answer": "I truly don't think about it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 42, "question": "How could she not be given the product of her parents, two of the coolest people?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 43, "answer": "OK, OK, I'll buy that one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "Coolness runs in the genes, doesn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "A little bit.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 50, "question": "How do you effortlessly, without any effort, get to be cool?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 51, "answer": "What would make you cool is the fact that you don't try.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "VBZ", ":", "IN", "POS", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 52, "question": "I'm trying too hard?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 53, "answer": "That's what's -- that's what's wonderful about people.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 92, "question": "Your mom, from what I've gleaned, a softer character?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 93, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 103, "question": "I mean how old were you when that happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "WRB", "DT", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 104, "answer": "I was 21.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 111, "question": "What effect did it have on you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 112, "answer": "It had a very deep effect on me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 124, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 125, "answer": "With me in her arms, like ringing the bell.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "``", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 126, "question": "With you in her arms?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 127, "answer": "Which always reminds me that scene from \"Goodfellas.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 137, "question": "To you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 138, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 154, "question": "An emotional barrier?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 155, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 157, "question": "So when you had this time with him, when he knew he was dying, do you think because he realized he wasn't going to be around, this was the last chance to have that conversation with you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 158, "answer": "I think he -- I think he honestly had a spiritual awakening because he -- you know, and I don't want to paint him as this, you know, horrible man.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 167, "question": "What did he say to you when he finally opened up?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "He made mistakes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 180, "question": "Was your mother still alive?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 181, "answer": "And you know -- no, she wasn't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 186, "question": "-- amazing time with your father?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 187, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "How would she felt about that, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "Wonderful.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 220, "question": "What are the chances of that, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "And she was in real life.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 245, "question": "Did they try and protest about it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "JJS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 246, "answer": "Most definitely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 256, "question": "Did you get picked on at all once the TV show took off?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 257, "answer": "Yes, but harmless.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Europe"]}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 261, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 262, "answer": "Well, it's funny because I -- you know, I've been in Europe touring a lot touring lately.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 297, "question": "Do you know Obama?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 298, "answer": "I don't know him.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 307, "question": "You know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 308, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 310, "question": "So that was right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "Exactly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "It wasn't Michelle, was it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "No, no, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michelle"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 338, "question": "And what is that, Piers?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 339, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "RB", "VB", "CC", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 349, "question": "How do I feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 350, "answer": "ORGAN: Don't try and be too modest.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 353, "question": "What did your mother tell you about women and how to treat them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 354, "answer": "Well, to treat them with respect and so forth.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "Have you got anyone?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "I would -- I would like it to change.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "What is it you love about women?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "I just love women.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "Am I easy to be with?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "Because you seem so effortlessly charming.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 384, "question": "I mean do you -- does that concern you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 385, "answer": "Completely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 399, "question": "Twenty-one?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 400, "answer": "Twenty-one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 405, "question": "What did it do, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 406, "answer": "It put something in me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "Was there a moment for you when you did something and you thought, my father was right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 423, "question": "Famous sex symbols?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 424, "answer": "People are people.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 440, "question": "But do you dream, you know, wistfully of getting married, having more children, that kind of conventional thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "VBN", ",", "VBG", "JJR", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 441, "answer": "I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 455, "question": "But what went wrong there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "JJ", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 456, "answer": ": Young.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 457, "question": "Too young?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "Young.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 475, "question": "Are you happy or are you concerned?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 476, "answer": "I'm not concerned at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 481, "question": "It's not easy, is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 482, "answer": "No, it's not easy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", ",", "JJ", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "Are you a good dad, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "As my mother said, self-praise is no recommendation.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "I'll pin Zoe down and said how goofy does your dad get?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "IN", "CC", "VBD", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "You'll have to ask her.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 520, "question": "Your family came to Hollywood when you were how old?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "TO", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 521, "answer": "Eleven.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Hollywood"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 528, "question": "What was it like for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 529, "answer": "I remember the first day it was quite strange.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 554, "question": "Who are the most naturally gifted artists you've encountered in your lifetime?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "RBS", "RB", "VBN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 555, "answer": "So many.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 565, "question": "What is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 566, "answer": "You can't really name it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NN", ",", "NN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 567, "question": "Can you describe it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 568, "answer": "It's just that thing, something special.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 571, "question": "What was the moment for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 572, "answer": "I don't know if I've ever come to that point.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 575, "question": "You don't think you're a star?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 576, "answer": "I'm -- somehow I'm always still that kid who was trying to get the record deal.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 578, "question": "Is that insecurity or is it hard work?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 579, "answer": "I think I put myself up -- I put myself up against the greatest people, these people that I mentioned, these people that influenced me that are amazing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 601, "question": "What was he like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 602, "answer": "He was very much like he is now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 616, "question": "Who has more tattoos?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJR", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 617, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 620, "question": "You have a whopping Jesus Christ on your back, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 621, "answer": "Not actually, the words.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 623, "question": "How many have you got?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 624, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 628, "question": "Have you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 629, "answer": "Not all of them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 631, "question": "So who has taken more drugs, you or Slash?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJR", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 632, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 638, "question": "Is it -- is the drugs process that so many musicians go through, is it tangibly better for creative music making?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", ":", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", "NN", "WDT", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "RBR", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 639, "answer": "I suppose at the time I thought it was.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 646, "question": "All day long?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 647, "answer": "All day long.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 655, "question": "And what does that do to you over time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 656, "answer": "Well, it just basically puts this wall of fuzz around you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 661, "question": "Are you pretty clean these days?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 662, "answer": "Oh, yeah, yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 663, "question": "Do you ever go recklessly partying?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 664, "answer": "Not really.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 676, "question": "What have you got in there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 677, "answer": "I have some stuff.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 678, "question": "Any Litore (ph)?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", "."], "aSentId": 679, "answer": "Of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 680, "question": "'61?", "question_pos_tagged": ["-NONE-", "."], "aSentId": 681, "answer": "Of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 682, "question": "Wow, really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 683, "answer": "Of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 710, "question": "A very powerful movie that, wasn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 711, "answer": "That was a beautiful experience.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 734, "question": "But what's the career moment where if you had the chance, you'd relive it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WRB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 735, "answer": "The career moment.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Jackson"]}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", ":", "RB", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 738, "question": "What was the biggest pinch?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 739, "answer": "Being -- probably producing Michael Jackson.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jackson"]}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 741, "question": "What made it so extraordinary?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 742, "answer": "Well, the fact that, you know, I wouldn't be here today if I hadn't seen the Jackson Five when I was six years old.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 792, "question": "Do you think of our lifetime, Michael Jackson was the best?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "."], "aSentId": 793, "answer": "RAVITZ: Of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Jackson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 795, "question": "The greatest naturally gifted, as you said earlier?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "RB", "VBN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RBR", "."], "aSentId": 796, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 797, "question": "Entertainer of them all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 798, "answer": "Yes, completely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]